Get your fill
Sausage Party is a adventure, animation, comedy film directed by Greg Tiernan.
Hot dog Frank leads a group of supermarket products on a quest to discover the truth about their
existence and what really happens when they become chosen to leave the grocery store.
Frank / Sergeant Pepper / Peanut Butter (voice), played by Seth Rogen.
Brenda (voice), played by Kristen Wiig.
Carl (voice), played by Jonah Hill.
Firewater / Tequila / El Guaco (voice), played by Bill Hader.
Barry (voice), played by Michael Cera.
Druggie (voice), played by James Franco.
Sausage Party is a 2016 adult animated comedy film directed by Conrad Vernon and Greg
Tiernan, and written by Kyle Hunter, Ariel Shaffir, Seth Rogen and Evan Goldberg.
A co-production between Canada and the United States, the film features the voices of Rogen, Kristen Wiig, Jonah Hill, Bill Hader, Michael
Cera, James Franco, Danny McBride, Craig Robinson, Paul Rudd, Nick Kroll, David Krumholtz, Edward Norton and Salma Hayek.
The film follows an anthropomorphic sausage who lives in a supermarket and goes on a
journey with his friends to escape their fate as groceries eaten by humans.
The film's animation was handled by the Vancouver-based Nitrogen Studios.
It is the first computer-animated film in both United States and Canada to
be rated R by the Motion Picture Association of America.
The film's rough cut premiered on March 14, 2016, at South by Southwest, followed by its general
theatrical release in the United States on August 12, 2016, by Columbia Pictures.
Sausage Party received generally positive reviews from critics and grossed $141 million against a budget of $19 million, surpassing
South Park: Bigger, Longer, and Uncut (1999) as the highest-grossing R-rated animated film at the time of its release.
A sequel television series, Sausage Party: Foodtopia, was released in 2024.
The film explores themes of supermarket, parody,
anthropomorphism, sausage, food.
The tone is lighthearted.